With the sweat glands in your feet, there's approximately nine thousand in each foot.
We discussed that you eliminate toxins from your sweat, from your breath and different areas.
We have a treatment that we use; an ionic charge which is a very slight regulated electronic charge through salt water and it helps pull out waste products from the sweat in your feet through the sweat glands.
The different colors that are distributed in the water; there may be an amber color, it may be black, it may have a floating foam and these different colors and these different elements that appear in water which originally started out clear are waste products from your circulatory system.
Your blood goes through your feet every seven minutes so to think that it also helps clean your blood.
We use this treatment on people that have foot pain, that have Planter Fasciitis and also have general aches and pains and it helps detoxify and helps them heal up quicker.
The colors, the browns, the blacks and the foamy are products and waste products from the liver and from the circulation and the oxidized waste and waste from the lymph.
So, as you'll notice on the water, you'll see the waste.
As the feet are in the water; the feet almost become invisible underneath the shroud of the waste products.
It's almost inconceivable that this much waste could be inside your body and you certainly wouldn't drink it.
We pour it down a drain.